Office of Undergraduate Education Records UA049
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student files, 1985 -- 2013; UA049.005; 31.75 Linear Feet
  - Baek, Bryant E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Bailey, Alex E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - Baker, John E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Baran, Thomas A. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - Barbero, Cristopher F. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Baron, Matthew E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00014 (Box 60)
  - Benson, Ryan E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00015 (Box 60)
  - Benson, Theo E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00016 (Box 60)
  - Betz, Martha E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00017 (Box 60)
  - Bill, Rachel E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00018 (Box 60)
  - Bjerke, Sean T. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00019 (Box 60)
  - Blake, Melanie E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00020 (Box 60)
  - Blumberg, Mike E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00021 (Box 60)
  - Boudreau, Laura M. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00022 (Box 60)
  - Bradley, Clifton III E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00023 (Box 60)
  - Brown, Nathan C. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00024 (Box 60)
  - Bruch, Kurt O. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00025 (Box 60)
  - Buch, Karen E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00026 (Box 60)
  - Bur, Andres M. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00027 (Box 60)
  - Burke, James (Jimmy) E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00028 (Box 60)
  - Burlingame, Sam E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00029 (Box 60)
  - Calabrese, Lee A. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00030 (Box 60)
  - Caldwell, Casey H. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00031 (Box 60)
  - Cappadona, Jim E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00032 (Box 60)
  - Caputo, Lauren R. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00033 (Box 60)
  - Cava, Laura E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00034 (Box 60)
  - Chow, Jon W. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00035 (Box 60)
  - Chrisco, Zachary P. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00036 (Box 60)
  - Cladouhos, Camille L. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00037 (Box 60)
  - Clark, Kelly A. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00038 (Box 60)
  - Moerlein, Alex W. E'04, 2004; UA049.005.060.00039 (Box 60)
  - Mueller, Andrew J. E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00040 (Box 60)
  - Mueller, Stuart A. E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00041 (Box 60)
  - Nangeroni, Paul E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00042 (Box 60)
  - Nercessian, Armen E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00043 (Box 60)
  - Ng, David E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00044 (Box 60)
  - Osser, Rosie E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00045 (Box 60)
  - Parimi, Sanjay E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00046 (Box 60)
  - Rowell, Adam E'05, 2005; UA049.005.060.00047 (Box 60)
  - Gowa, John E'10, 2011; UA049.005.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Gray, Gilad A. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Greenfield, Anna E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Gregory, Benjamin L. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - Gudjohnsen, Joshua E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - Gudrais, Laila L. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - Harkness, Ty E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - Harper, Eric E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - Harris, Oliver C. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - Hart, Colleen E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Hawkins, Brendan E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Hessler, David E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - Hitov, Benjamin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - Hofsetter, Ryan E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - Hong, Ed E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - Hull, Lindsay A. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - Inonu, Murat E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - James, Anthony E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - Jackson, Michael E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - Jih, Daniel E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Kang, Urey E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00021 (Box 61)
  - Kelly, Matthew E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00022 (Box 61)
  - Kessler, Benjamin S. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Kim, Andrew E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Kleinberg, Jamie E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Krommenhoek, Kerina E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Ladue, Arlin W. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00027 (Box 61)
  - Lannin, Timothy B. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00028 (Box 61)
  - Latina, Christopher E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00029 (Box 61)
  - Leach, Olivia E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00030 (Box 61)
  - Liao, Liwei E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00031 (Box 61)
  - Lines, Austin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00032 (Box 61)
  - Liu, Qianwen E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00033 (Box 61)
  - Lohmann, Jenna E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00034 (Box 61)
  - Luks, Valerie E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00035 (Box 61)
  - Mailand, Deb E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00036 (Box 61)
  - Matungulu, Ilankir E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00037 (Box 61)
  - Mariano, Kevin M. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00038 (Box 61)
  - Mason, George (Sam) E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00039 (Box 61)
  - Mayerson, Edward B. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00040 (Box 61)
  - McKay, Chris E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00041 (Box 61)
  - McKelvy, Patrick E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00042 (Box 61)
  - Melnick, Corey E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00043 (Box 61)
  - Menning, Matt E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00044 (Box 61)
  - Meyendorff, Andrew E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00045 (Box 61)
  - Meyer, David E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00046 (Box 61)
  - Meyer, Zach E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00047 (Box 61)
  - Montana, Jessica E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00048 (Box 61)
  - Morgan, Bailey E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00049 (Box 61)
  - Morris, Luke E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00050 (Box 61)
  - Motola - Barnes, Michael E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00051 (Box 61)
  - Nectow, Alex E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00052 (Box 61)
  - Nelson, Ryan T. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00053 (Box 61)
  - Nickels, Ford E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00054 (Box 61)
  - Neuhs, Thomas C. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00055 (Box 61)
  - Ngu, Huy E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00056 (Box 61)
  - Nichols-Schmolze, Kyle E'11, 2011; UA049.005.061.00057 (Box 61)
  - Nimocks, Robert T. (Mitchell) E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Nixon, Laura J. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Noble, Jessica L. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Nochlin, Jason E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - Okparaeke, Ebere E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Orendoff, Ryan E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Oshinsky, Miriam E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Owens, Christian E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - Park, Doohyun E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Patel, Atur E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Patterson, Colin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Pedevillano, Paul E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Pellittieri, Anthony C. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Pesch, Meghan A. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Peterson, Jeremy E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - Pham, Vinh E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Proulx, Kevin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Quinn, Andrew E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Ragazzini, Jeffrey M. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Reif, Katie E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Rice, Chris E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Rizzolo, Rob E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Rodkey, Daniel E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00023 (Box 62)
  - Rosenfield, Matt E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Rye, Caitlin E'10, 2011; UA049.005.062.00025 (Box 62)
  - Sahin, Kerem E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00026 (Box 62)
  - Sanders, Trevor E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00027 (Box 62)
  - Sayler, Andrew E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00028 (Box 62)
  - Segal, Benjamin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00029 (Box 62)
  - Simon, Anna E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00030 (Box 62)
  - Skalina, Karin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00031 (Box 62)
  - Smith, Kelly E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00032 (Box 62)
  - Spencer, Abigail E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00033 (Box 62)
  - Stack, Trevor E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00034 (Box 62)
  - Stewart, Eric A. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00035 (Box 62)
  - Sullivan, Nicholas E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00036 (Box 62)
  - Swanson, Catherine E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00037 (Box 62)
  - Tam, Bonita W. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00038 (Box 62)
  - Tam, Stephanie E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00039 (Box 62)
  - Tang, Sai E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00040 (Box 62)
  - Tetler, James E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00041 (Box 62)
  - Tucker, Lia E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00042 (Box 62)
  - Tusavul, Suzan E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00043 (Box 62)
  - Valentin, Thomas E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00044 (Box 62)
  - Vidich, Paul E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00045 (Box 62)
  - Vizner, Michael (Miki) E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00046 (Box 62)
  - Vorlicek, Christopher E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00047 (Box 62)
  - Wagner, Julie E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00048 (Box 62)
  - Walker, Andrew M E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00049 (Box 62)
  - Wallace, Emma E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00050 (Box 62)
  - Walsh, Jessica E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00051 (Box 62)
  - Watanasiri, Justin E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00052 (Box 62)
  - Weixel, Evan E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00053 (Box 62)
  - Wells, Daniel J. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00054 (Box 62)
  - Wickert, Karen E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00055 (Box 62)
  - Wilner, Joshua E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00056 (Box 62)
  - Wilson, Stephen E. E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00057 (Box 62)
  - Wolfand, Jordyn E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00058 (Box 62)
  - Wong, Monica E'11, 2011; UA049.005.062.00059 (Box 62)
  - Al-Majali, Zain, 2012; UA049.005.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Anderson, Emily, 2012; UA049.005.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Anton, Christen M., 2012; UA049.005.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Arena, Jeff, 2012; UA049.005.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Armando, John, 2012; UA049.005.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - Aryanpur, Rameen, 2012; UA049.005.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Bai, Michael, 2012; UA049.005.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - Bargar, Cliff, 2012; UA049.005.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - Battra, Richa, 2012; UA049.005.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Bernstein, Michael J., 2012; UA049.005.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - Bergin, Kylee, 2012; UA049.005.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - Berzan, Constantin, 2012; UA049.005.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - Birger, Jack, 2012; UA049.005.063.00013 (Box 63)
  - Bixenstine, Nathan, 2012; UA049.005.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - Booras, Kathryn, 2012; UA049.005.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - Boudreau, Sarah, 2012; UA049.005.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - Boutin, Kyle, 2012; UA049.005.063.00017 (Box 63)
  - Bradley, Cameron, 2012; UA049.005.063.00018 (Box 63)
  - Brereton, George, 2012; UA049.005.063.00019 (Box 63)
  - Brinson, Andrew, 2012; UA049.005.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - Cassidy, Brynne M., 2012; UA049.005.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - Cassidy, Patrick D., 2012; UA049.005.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - Celozzi, Anthony, 2012; UA049.005.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - Ching, Brandon, 2012; UA049.005.063.00024 (Box 63)
  - Chu, Chak (Michael), 2012; UA049.005.063.00025 (Box 63)
  - Chung, Wenshiang, 2012; UA049.005.063.00026 (Box 63)
  - Cilley, Bri, 2012; UA049.005.063.00027 (Box 63)
  - Collins, Caitlin L., 2012; UA049.005.063.00028 (Box 63)
  - Coonahan, Erin, 2012; UA049.005.063.00029 (Box 63)
  - Cousens, Zachary F., 2012; UA049.005.063.00030 (Box 63)
  - Croteau, Nick, 2012; UA049.005.063.00031 (Box 63)
  - Curless, William G., 2012; UA049.005.063.00032 (Box 63)
  - Darveau, Katherine, 2012; UA049.005.063.00033 (Box 63)
  - Dave, Hershal, 2012; UA049.005.063.00034 (Box 63)
  - Dincer, Omer, 2012; UA049.005.063.00035 (Box 63)
  - Doisneau, Anne, 2012; UA049.005.063.00036 (Box 63)
  - Donahue, Kyle L., 2012; UA049.005.063.00037 (Box 63)
  - Donovan, Ian M., 2012; UA049.005.063.00038 (Box 63)
  - Dove, Natalie B., 2012; UA049.005.063.00039 (Box 63)
  - Eacret, Valerie, 2012; UA049.005.063.00040 (Box 63)
  - El Gazayerli, Omar, 2012; UA049.005.063.00041 (Box 63)
  - Eng, Daniel, 2012; UA049.005.063.00042 (Box 63)
  - Flament, Lauren, 2012; UA049.005.063.00043 (Box 63)
  - Flanagen, Kelly, 2012; UA049.005.063.00044 (Box 63)
  - Foglietta, Steven, 2012; UA049.005.063.00045 (Box 63)
  - Formell, Erik, 2012; UA049.005.063.00046 (Box 63)
  - Frisell, Maren, 2012; UA049.005.063.00047 (Box 63)
  - Fuchs, Nicholas, 2012; UA049.005.063.00048 (Box 63)
  - Galvin, Matt L., 2012; UA049.005.063.00049 (Box 63)
  - Garcia, Yorman, 2012; UA049.005.063.00050 (Box 63)
  - Gardner, Chris, 2012; UA049.005.063.00051 (Box 63)
  - Glassner, Austin, 2012; UA049.005.063.00052 (Box 63)
  - Goldenberg, Matthew, 2012; UA049.005.063.00053 (Box 63)
  - Graziano, Elliott, 2012; UA049.005.063.00054 (Box 63)
  - Griffin, Riley, 2012; UA049.005.063.00055 (Box 63)
  - Gudjohnsen, Jonathan, 2012; UA049.005.063.00056 (Box 63)
  - Gurdo, Stephen A., 2012; UA049.005.063.00057 (Box 63)
  - Halpert, Daniel, 2012; UA049.005.063.00058 (Box 63)
  - Hariri, Sara, 2012; UA049.005.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Henderson, Hannah C., 2012; UA049.005.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Hernandez, Katherine, 2012; UA049.005.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Hill, Abbie, 2012; UA049.005.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Hopkins, Calvin, 2012; UA049.005.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Huang, Jason, 2012; UA049.005.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Huang, Yunlin, 2012; UA049.005.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Huh, Yun-Sook, 2012; UA049.005.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Hussain, Ahmed, 2012; UA049.005.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Imlay, Ashton, 2012; UA049.005.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - Iuppa, Elizabeth, 2012; UA049.005.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - John, Esha, 2012; UA049.005.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - Johnson, Eric S., 2012; UA049.005.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Kadoko, Jonah, 2012; UA049.005.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Kallitsantsis, Paris, 2012; UA049.005.064.00015 (Box 64)
  - Kaminski, Jared A., 2012; UA049.005.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - Kaslowski, Lara, 2012; UA049.005.064.00017 (Box 64)
  - Keches, Dan, 2012; UA049.005.064.00018 (Box 64)
  - Keene, Robert W., 2012; UA049.005.064.00019 (Box 64)
  - Kempe, Doug, 2012; UA049.005.064.00020 (Box 64)
  - Khaku, Ammar, 2012; UA049.005.064.00021 (Box 64)
  - Kilroy, Jared, 2012; UA049.005.064.00022 (Box 64)
  - Klinker, Lauren, 2012; UA049.005.064.00023 (Box 64)
  - Kocak, Daniel (Derwan), 2012; UA049.005.064.00024 (Box 64)
  - Koltai, Benjamin, 2012; UA049.005.064.00025 (Box 64)
  - Kudlack, Chris, 2012; UA049.005.064.00026 (Box 64)
  - Lade Jr., Robert K., 2012; UA049.005.064.00027 (Box 64)
  - LaHart, Cameron, 2012; UA049.005.064.00028 (Box 64)
  - Langford, William K., 2012; UA049.005.064.00029 (Box 64)
  - Ledoux, Edward W., 2012; UA049.005.064.00030 (Box 64)
  - Lessard, Joe, 2011; UA049.005.064.00031 (Box 64)
  - Leung, Raymond, 2012; UA049.005.064.00032 (Box 64)
  - Levasseur, Nicole, 2012; UA049.005.064.00033 (Box 64)
  - Levinsky, Ian, 2012; UA049.005.064.00034 (Box 64)
  - Liao, John S., 2012; UA049.005.064.00035 (Box 64)
  - Lieman-Sifry, Mina, 2012; UA049.005.064.00036 (Box 64)
  - Lim, Timothy, 2012; UA049.005.064.00037 (Box 64)
  - Lin, Tony Hongtong, 2012; UA049.005.064.00038 (Box 64)
  - Lind, Rachel, 2012; UA049.005.064.00039 (Box 64)
  - Livne, Shir, 2012; UA049.005.064.00040 (Box 64)
  - Lo, Xu Yi Ian, 2012; UA049.005.064.00041 (Box 64)
  - Luo, Yun, 2012; UA049.005.064.00042 (Box 64)
  - MacNaughton, Piers, 2012; UA049.005.064.00043 (Box 64)
  - Magden, Emir, 2012; UA049.005.064.00044 (Box 64)
  - Marshall, Ryan, 2012; UA049.005.064.00045 (Box 64)
  - McArthur, Scott, 2012; UA049.005.064.00046 (Box 64)
  - McCormick, Kevin, 2012; UA049.005.064.00047 (Box 64)
  - Meer, Daniel, 2012; UA049.005.064.00048 (Box 64)
  - Metcalf, Christian (Luke), 2012; UA049.005.064.00049 (Box 64)
  - Miaoulis, Marina, 2012; UA049.005.064.00050 (Box 64)
  - Michael, Alix, 2012; UA049.005.064.00051 (Box 64)
  - Milando, Chad, 2012; UA049.005.064.00052 (Box 64)
  - Minden, Victor, 2012; UA049.005.064.00053 (Box 64)
  - Miyasaka, Shuhei, 2012; UA049.005.064.00054 (Box 64)
  - Mogenson, Mike, 2011; UA049.005.064.00055 (Box 64)
  - Monzon, Anna, 2012; UA049.005.064.00056 (Box 64)
  - Morrissey, Kevin, 2012; UA049.005.064.00057 (Box 64)
  - Mutzel, Christopher, 2012; UA049.005.064.00058 (Box 64)
  - Nilan, Sean, 2012; UA049.005.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - Olson, Woyd, 2012; UA049.005.065.00002 (Box 65)
  - Olsen, Rebecca, 2012; UA049.005.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - Osborne, Matthew, 2012; UA049.005.065.00004 (Box 65)
  - Pace, Carolyn, 2012; UA049.005.065.00005 (Box 65)
  - Papa, Kristina M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00006 (Box 65)
  - Parisi, Erika, 2012; UA049.005.065.00007 (Box 65)
  - Parker, Amanda M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00008 (Box 65)
  - Pellegrini, Andrew, 2012; UA049.005.065.00009 (Box 65)
  - Perez, Kelvin, 2012; UA049.005.065.00010 (Box 65)
  - Perkins, Jess, 2012; UA049.005.065.00011 (Box 65)
  - Perkins, Taylor, 2012; UA049.005.065.00012 (Box 65)
  - Perry, Natalie, 2012; UA049.005.065.00013 (Box 65)
  - Pellerteri, Will, 2012; UA049.005.065.00014 (Box 65)
  - Pinals, Lisa, 2012; UA049.005.065.00015 (Box 65)
  - Powell, Charles, 2012; UA049.005.065.00016 (Box 65)
  - Prescott, Jeffry M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00017 (Box 65)
  - Purcell, Andrew, 2012; UA049.005.065.00018 (Box 65)
  - Qiu, Junhui, 2012; UA049.005.065.00019 (Box 65)
  - Raisbeck, Daniel B., 2012; UA049.005.065.00020 (Box 65)
  - Ramjattan, Sanya, 2012; UA049.005.065.00021 (Box 65)
  - Ren, Shuo, 2012; UA049.005.065.00022 (Box 65)
  - Ribadeneira, Martin, 2012; UA049.005.065.00023 (Box 65)
  - Richmond, Matthew, 2012; UA049.005.065.00024 (Box 65)
  - Riker, Katherine, 2012; UA049.005.065.00025 (Box 65)
  - Rizzo, Daniel, 2012; UA049.005.065.00026 (Box 65)
  - Rosen, Matt, 2012; UA049.005.065.00027 (Box 65)
  - Rosenfeld, Asher, 2012; UA049.005.065.00028 (Box 65)
  - Roth, Keegan, 2012; UA049.005.065.00029 (Box 65)
  - Ryan, David M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00030 (Box 65)
  - Said, Firas, 2012; UA049.005.065.00031 (Box 65)
  - Salisbury, Will, 2012; UA049.005.065.00032 (Box 65)
  - Sanariya, Chandni, 2012; UA049.005.065.00033 (Box 65)
  - Schick, Emily W., 2012; UA049.005.065.00034 (Box 65)
  - Schulte, Mark, 2012; UA049.005.065.00035 (Box 65)
  - Sebik, Joanna, 2012; UA049.005.065.00036 (Box 65)
  - Shah, Adhvait, 2012; UA049.005.065.00037 (Box 65)
  - Shah, Rushabh, 2012; UA049.005.065.00038 (Box 65)
  - Shaukat, Farhan, 2012; UA049.005.065.00039 (Box 65)
  - Shaw, Emily, 2012; UA049.005.065.00040 (Box 65)
  - Sheldon III, Robert J., 2012; UA049.005.065.00041 (Box 65)
  - Sheneman, Brad, 2012; UA049.005.065.00042 (Box 65)
  - Siebert, Sean M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00043 (Box 65)
  - Siegel, Michael, 2012; UA049.005.065.00044 (Box 65)
  - Staschke, Leah, 2012; UA049.005.065.00045 (Box 65)
  - Stone, Nicholas, 2012; UA049.005.065.00046 (Box 65)
  - Story, Evan, 2012; UA049.005.065.00047 (Box 65)
  - Strittmatter, William (Alex), 2012; UA049.005.065.00048 (Box 65)
  - Suhonen, Christine E., 2012; UA049.005.065.00049 (Box 65)
  - Tang, Katherine M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00050 (Box 65)
  - Tang, Phillip, 2012; UA049.005.065.00051 (Box 65)
  - Thacher, Kory, 2012; UA049.005.065.00052 (Box 65)
  - Thompson, Jamie, 2012; UA049.005.065.00053 (Box 65)
  - Thorup, Jessie, 2012; UA049.005.065.00054 (Box 65)
  - Trevarrow, Cristina, 2012; UA049.005.065.00055 (Box 65)
  - Trombetta, John J., 2012; UA049.005.065.00056 (Box 65)
  - Varney, Christopher M., 2012; UA049.005.065.00057 (Box 65)
  - Tully, Roxanne, 2012; UA049.005.065.00058 (Box 65)
  - Turner, Marc, 2012; UA049.005.065.00059 (Box 65)
  - Vastola, Mike, 2012; UA049.005.065.00060 (Box 65)
  - Vaughan, Sam, 2012; UA049.005.066.00001 (Box Shared 73)
  - Voorhis, Jimmy, 2012; UA049.005.066.00002 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wahrenberger, Allison, 2012; UA049.005.066.00003 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wang, David E., 2012; UA049.005.066.00004 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wang, Rebecca, 2012; UA049.005.066.00005 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wang, Yushi, 2012; UA049.005.066.00006 (Box Shared 73)
  - Ward, Andrew, 2012; UA049.005.066.00007 (Box Shared 73)
  - Warnick, Jeffrey D., 2012; UA049.005.066.00008 (Box Shared 73)
  - Weeks, Jesse, 2012; UA049.005.066.00009 (Box Shared 73)
  - White, Zach, 2012; UA049.005.066.00010 (Box Shared 73)
  - Whitney, David J., 2012; UA049.005.066.00011 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wilburn, Eric, 2012; UA049.005.066.00012 (Box Shared 73)
  - Willen, Michael, 2012; UA049.005.066.00013 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wilson, Danielle L., 2012; UA049.005.066.00014 (Box Shared 73)
  - Wooldridge, John, 2012; UA049.005.066.00015 (Box Shared 73)
  - Work, John, 2012; UA049.005.066.00016 (Box Shared 73)
  - Yi, Michael C., 2012; UA049.005.066.00017 (Box Shared 73)
  - Zak, Marianna, 2012; UA049.005.066.00018 (Box Shared 73)
  - Zheng, Weiyi (Edward), 2012; UA049.005.066.00019 (Box Shared 73)
- Degree Sheets, 2003 -- 2011; UA049.006; 33.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains degree sheets, many of which have transcripts attached, from the Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Education.
  - Ab-Al, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - Abad-Manterola, Ines, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00001 (Box 28)
    - Abraham, Amy Susan, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00002 (Box 28)
    - Abraham, Wendy Elizabeth, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00003 (Box 28)
    - Abdul-Aziz, Rana E., 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00004 (Box 28)
    - Ackerman, Elliot Leedom, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00005 (Box 28)
    - Adamchuk, Michael Paul, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00006 (Box 28)
    - Ades, Daniel, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00007 (Box 28)
    - Adigun, Sijuwola Oladejo, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00008 (Box 28)
    - Affel, Marjorie Ellen, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00009 (Box 28)
    - Afshar, Afsoon, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00010 (Box 28)
    - Agrawal, Natasha Kishore, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00011 (Box 28)
    - Aguiling, Sheryl Bona, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00012 (Box 28)
    - Ahn, Jacqueline, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00013 (Box 28)
    - Akim, Yelena, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00014 (Box 28)
    - Al-Adawi, Waqas Suleiman, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00015 (Box 28)
    - Alansari, Sami Mahmood, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00016 (Box 28)
    - Alborelli, Rodolfo, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00017 (Box 28)
    - Al-Dawalibi, Maarouf, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00018 (Box 28)
    - Alderman, Jesse Harlan, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00019 (Box 28)
    - Aldrich, Lindsey Ann, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00020 (Box 28)
    - Alford, Matthew Scott, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00021 (Box 28)
    - Alireza, Mishaal Fahd, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00022 (Box 28)
    - Alonso-Mendoza, Bianca Marina, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00023 (Box 28)
    - Altman, Alexandra Bernette, 2003; UA049.006.028.00001.00024 (Box 28)
  - Am-Az, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - Amdur, Thomas Jay, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00001 (Box 28)
    - Anderson, Kathryn Marguerite, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00002 (Box 28)
    - Anderson, Mary Anne, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00003 (Box 28)
    - Anderson, Taylor William, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00004 (Box 28)
    - Andrews, Anne Elizabeth, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00005 (Box 28)
    - Applestein, Laura Meredith, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00006 (Box 28)
    - Apraku, Akua Akyampomaa, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00007 (Box 28)
    - Aranson, Joel Charles, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00008 (Box 28)
    - Araujo, Andrea Rivero, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00009 (Box 28)
    - Archambault, Allison Marie, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00010 (Box 28)
    - Arena, Paul Joseph, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00011 (Box 28)
    - Arinello, James Laurence, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00012 (Box 28)
    - Asarch, Adam Daniel, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00013 (Box 28)
    - Ashikalis, Kyriakos, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00014 (Box 28)
    - Asfour, Lana Farid, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00015 (Box 28)
    - Attanasio, David Louis, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00016 (Box 28)
    - Azi, Tamilla Denise, 2003; UA049.006.028.00002.00017 (Box 28)
  - B-Ba, 2003; UA049.006.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - Badri, Hadi Mohammed Taher, 2003; UA049.006.028.00003.00001 (Box 28)
    - Bae, Junho, 2003; UA049.006.028.00003.00002 (Box 28)